#### Contact

spoiledsweet1@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/staceyhamilton-hanna-896b1877 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Critical Care
ACLS
EHR

# Stacey Hamilton-Hanna

Clinical Informatics Program Manager at Dignity Health Sacramento, California

### Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Critical Care, Cerner, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing from California State University-Sacramento.

## Experience

Dignity Health 20 years 8 months

Clinical Informatics Program Manager November 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)

Clinical Informatics Nurse

Greater Sacramento Service Area

December 2011 - November 2016 (5 years)

Critical Care Nurse
December 1999 - December 2011 (12 years 1 month)

### Education

California State University-Sacramento
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing
Research and Clinical Nursing · (1994 - 1999)